There is a young couple - your wife is beats you all the time.
Come out.
Prophesy Confirmation
My name is Ogbe Emmanuel.
I'm the one the man of God prophesied about that his wife always beats him.
Each time I and my wife have a little quarrel or I want to correct her,
she will not listen to me.
Just a little correction – she would beat me.
Two months ago, she beat me on the mouth and blood started gushing out.
She does not have affection for me.
Since I married her in 2015, I have never felt like a married man.
How does a married man feel?
They feel happy with their wives.
Prophecy Time
So, she used to beat you.
Yes, very well, man of God.
My name is Obiora Edith,
You used to beat your husband.
Yes, whenever I am angry, I slap him.
Most of the time, I get angry when I am close to him. I don’t know why.
Get close to him and see whether...
The SCOAN Sunday Service
TESTIMONY TIME
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
We are Mr & Mrs Obiora Emmanuel.
We thank God for today, for the deliverance that God has given us last week, on Sunday.
Last Sunday, during the mass prayer, man of God prophesied
and pointed his hand towards the area where I was.
He said there was a young couple over there; the wife always beat the husband.
Mr & Mrs Obiora Emmanuel
Prophecy Testimony
I just thought about it for one minute, because I knew what was happening at my home.
Immediately, I jumped up from my seat.
As I was going around, towards that side...
They asked me to go and bring my wife.
While going there, I saw my wife coming out.
You are so happy, you are laughing and smiling today.
Yeah, I'm happy because I know I'm free.
Mr & Mrs Obiora Emmanuel
Prophecy Testimony
You know; man of God said that we were young.
Yeah, as you can see, I'm young, and my wife is very young, as well.
We got married in 2015.
To be frank with you - you could see me trying to explain to man of God that I never tasted a happy home.
Before I married my wife; I was raised in a Christian home, I always tried to follow the rules of God.
I prepared myself for this marriage.
There were many women, girls around me but I separated myself from them for one year,
in order to look for a good partner.
After that I checked myself very well, and I remembered this fine, beautiful lady standing here.
I decided to approach her by making a phone call.
During the first phone call conversation, I asked her if she would become my wife.
I married my wife and the trouble started.
At that time, my wife was very young, she just finished her secondary school.
Immediately we came to our house, she was in social media, always with her phone, busy.
She had no time for me.
I talked with her about that, asking her, "Please, leave this phone for some time. Let us talk.
Let us reason as husband and wife."
As I begged her, she refused to listen.
I told her that this thing she was doing - I also knew how to do it very well;
when I start doing it, there would be a "fire".
She refused.
I gave her time to stop but she refused.
Then, I started using social media on my new phone.
I was sending "friend requests" to different ladies.
As I started doing it, the "fire" began.
We were not listening to each other anymore.
I said, "OK, let me forget that one".
This happened at the very beginning of our marriage.
This lasted last year, and especially this year.
That is when I stared developing another habit of drinking alcohol.
This was caused by too much of disrespect, beating me...
You understand - we couldn't have talked; when I spoke, she spoke 20 times more.
When I tried to calm her down as a husband, getting near to her, asking what was the problem,
I would get a "bam".
To the glory of God; I thank God for being in The Synagogue today,
because I've been yearning to come here.
I knew that the man of God is the only person that could solve this problem.
Thank God for what happened last Sunday.
After the prophecy of last Sunday, I'm very happy with my wife.
Yesterday, we were walking towards that side - she held my hand here.
Mr & Mrs Obiora Emmanuel
Prophecy Testimony
Now, if you look...
Can you demonstrate what you are saying?
Like this.
You mean it was strange?
It was strange.
And she didn't look ashamed, she just focused on me.
You can see now - if you look at where we are sitting;
if she feels tired, she would be resting like this.
I'm very happy.
So, you mean that she never used to do all this before?
None of these things - I didn't deserve it.
Instead, it was beating...
Yeah, if she did like this by mistake, when she realised this, she would be like, "No, he doesn't deserve it."
You understand...
But I thank God; today I deserve all this.
Amen!
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
We are Mr & Mrs Obiora Emmanuel
Last Sunday, man of God gave us a prophecy.
It was after the mass prayer, I was sitting down, placing my head on the chair in front of me.
When I heard there was a couple, that the wife always beats, I was like, "Who does that?".
I raised up my head to know who the person was.
Then, I looked beside me and found out that my husband was no longer in the same place.
I said, "Wow, so, it is me."
Then, I said to myself that I was not going out, unless the usher comes and carries me out.
I couldn't see myself standing here.
For what?
I don't know what made me to carry my bag - they were big and heavy.
Before I passed I had to say, "Excuse me."
The space was just enough for me to pass.
When I came to the stage, I realised where I was.
I became more angry, like "What is this man saying?"
I was so angry at my husband.
After the prayer last Sunday, I see my husband as my husband.
Unlike before; whenever I was close to him, I was always sweating - I didn't know why,
even in the "air conditioned" place, I was always sweating.
One day, I asked him, "Don't you think it is a mistake, getting married to you?"
As I was sweating - imagine that.
Then he said I was not normal.
Then I realised I wasn't normal because I had a spiritual husband, which I knew.
I kept praying.
I thank God that after everything I came here and I was delivered.
Praise to Lord Jesus!
How do you beat your husband?
Whenever I was angry, because everything he did was "negative".
I didn't see "positive" in him.
Only when he was not around, I would see good and be like, "This man is really a good man".
But whenever he comes back...
I would be seeing another person.
Whenever he was talking to me, I would be saying, "Why is he giving me this advice?"
Instead of listening to what he was saying, I would keep remembering all that we were going through,
and I would be just like, "Leave me alone".
I would maybe slap him - I didn't know where my hand would go.
Sometimes, I didn't even know I beat him; I would just ask, "Did I just hit you?"
He would say, "No, you didn't beat me".
I thank God for today.
Thank you man of God.
Mr & Mrs Obiora Emmanuel
Prophecy Testimony
Thank you!
Mr & Mrs Obiora Emmanuel
Prophecy Testimony
TT: Jacqueline Margaret 08/09/18
RV ROBERT BEGIER 12/08/2018